https://www.questchat.com/privacy-policy/

Buy Minutes
No menu assigned!
QuestChat Privacy Policy
1. Acceptance
First Media Group, Inc. (“Us” “We”, “QuestChat) provides the QUESTCHAT mobile App, QuestChat IVR System and related website www.questchat.com. By using Quest, its App or website (“QuestChat”), you, the user, accept the Privacy Policy.
2. Modifications
It is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policy from time to time and to familiarize yourself with any modifications. Your continued use of QuestChat after such modifications will constitute your agreement to be bound by the modified Agreement.
3. Privacy Statement
This policy discloses QuestChat’s practices as to what information is collected by QuestChat:
a) What personal information is collected, how it is used and who it can be shared with;
b) The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information;
c) How to modify any inaccuracies in your personal information;
4. Adult Service
QuestChat does not knowingly collect information from or market to anyone under 18. You must agree you are 18 plus to use QuestChat.
5. Information Collection, Use and Sharing
QuestChat is the sole owner of the information collected to the site. Prior to making a profile while browsing QuestChat certain information is captured such as your:
• IP address
• Platform, operating system, and browser information
• Path through the Site
QuestChat collects personal information such as: in order to set up an account/membership and to provide you with exemplary ongoing service. We collect information that allows us to process your account/membership and to confirm your identity and email/phone number so that we can assist you knowing that you are who you say you are. This information includes your:
• Name
• Location
• Email address
• Age
• Gender
We do not sell or rent this information to other unaffiliated or third party organizations.
6. Security
Because some features and services on QuestChat are available for a fee, a Member may elect to purchase a subscription. QuestChat protects your sensitive information offline and online. Online: sensitive information such as credit card data is encrypted and transmitted securely in accordance with the best encryption software standard (SSL). Offline: Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (ie/ Customer Service Support to verify identity) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
7. Marketing to Members of QuestChat
When you become a member of “QuestChat” you have the right to receive information about your account, membership, new products or amendments and enhancement to the services as well as any upcoming promotions, specials and contests relating to QuestChat. QuestChat may conduct surveys or determine your preferences in order to better serve its members. Canadian Customers: As a QuestChat customer, we have the right to promote our services through SMS. You can text “STOP” to opt-out of further text message communications. As a US QuestChat customer who opts in to use our system, you have granted us the right to promote our services through SMS. You have the right to opt out an can do so at any time by replying “STOP” to our SMS message.  Standard message and data rates may apply.  Visit here for our full information on SMS.
8. Access to your Personal Information
You can unsubscribe or opt-out of future contact and promotions from QuestChat at any time. You can also have access and change/correct any data we have about you.
9. Exchange Monitoring
Members communicate directly with each other through QuestChat. QuestChat has the right but not the obligation to monitor all Customer Data, messages and public postings. Where, in our sole discretion, customer data, messages and public postings violate this agreement, or any applicable law, or may negatively affect the goodwill of QuestChat, this content may be deleted and/or reported to relevant authorities.
10. Disclosure to Law Enforcement
QuestChat may disclose any Customer Data in order to cooperate with relevant law enforcement authorities without further consent or notification to you, upon a lawful request from a Law Enforcement Agency. QuestChat may do so in the case of any systems or network security at other sites, for any violations of the law including of abusive conduct, fraudulent conduct or otherwise illegal activity or in the investigation of suspected criminal violations.
11. Cookies
In order to make your QuestChat website and mobile experience as seamless and enjoyable as possible, we use cookies. A cookie is a small bit of information that gets saved to your browser in order to allow us to auto-fill specific information, remember your preferences and create a more personalized experience. This is common practice with most websites and does not expose any personally identifiable information about you.
At any time, you can view and change the cookies stored in your browser by altering your browser settings.
The types of cookies that QuestChat uses include:
• Session Cookies which are deleted when you close your browser and are used to assist you in form completions and check out process and permit QuestChat to record the pages you’ve visited.
• Persistent Cookies which help you and QuestChat to keep and track preferences so you don’t repeatedly enter information such as city name; these cookies can be manually deleted at any.
• Security Cookies allow QuestChat to ensure that web transactions are valid, non-fraudulent and to keep your data protected from unauthorized parties.
• Session State/ Analytic cookies permits QuestChat to recognize popular pages popular pages on our website and common click paths,
12. Links
QuestChat may contain links to other Internet or mobile sites. QuestChat is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of such other sites. Please become aware of the privacy policies of such sites. QuestChat is not responsible for such policies and expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such policies.
13. Surveys and Contest
QuestChat, in providing members promotions and contests, may have no direct or indirect relationship, or affiliation with the company or corporation administering the promotions and contests, except where the prize consists of a gift certificate for use on the internet address www.QuestChat.com. Members should review the terms and rules of such promotions and contests for complete details about their participation and terms of participation. Members will not hold QuestChat liable for any damages, warranties or liability resulting from participating in any promotions or contests.
QuestChat collects personal information to process your entry and administer the contest/promotion. Personal information collected for contests/promotions becomes the property of QuestChat. On occasion, we undertake contests/promotions with sponsors or we use third parties to assist us in administering a contest/promotion. In these cases, we may share your personal information with these sponsors or administrators in order that they can assist us in undertaking and administering the contest/promotion. In addition, if you enter a contest or participate in a promotion that involves or relates to specific products, services or activities, we or our sponsors may send you material that relates to such products, services or activities.
14. Contact us
We will honour any requests you may have to access to or review your personal information or if you feel we are not abiding by our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices or you wish to restrict our use of your personal information discussed above, you may contact us in writing at the following address stating your request: QuestChat PRIVACY USAGE; 75 South Broadway, 4th floor White Plains, NY 10601, UNITED STATES or by calling our toll-free customer service center: 1.888.975.6565 or via email at customercare@questchat.com.
15. Commercial Electronic Messages
You may unsubscribe from receiving email communication from QuestChat at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link within any email from QuestChat. After clicking the link, you will see a thank you page and will no longer receive emails containing promos, specials or content from QuestChat. Please note that although you will be unsubscribed from receiving promos, specials and content you may continue to receive purchase-related notifications such as confirmation emails after making a web purchase.
You may unsubscribe from receiving SMS alerts from QuestChat at any time by texting STOP to 862666.  Standard message and data rates may apply.  You are welcome to contact QuestChat directly at help@questchat.com with any questions.
This Privacy Policy was last updated February 06, 2017
About
Why QuestChat
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Free Male Chat
QuestChat for Men
QuestChat for Women
© 2020 QuestChat | Free Trial Chat Line - Meet Local Singles. Must be 18+ to call the system or use the QuestChat app
